{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622507","name":"Xus China House Inc","address":"550 E Warren Ave","zipcode":"48201","owner":"Fang XU","licenseNumber":"218259","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"4/17/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000688A53EFC1C354C0F82FB0FEF72D4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43933","establishmentid":"51622507","name":"Xus China House Inc","inspectionDate":"2018-10-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"0","pfcount":"3","ccount":"4","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"4","correctedcritical":"3","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"43933","inspectionDate":"10/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622507","name":"Xus China House Inc","violationCode":"6-501.114","violationDescription":"The PREMISES shall be free of items that are unnecessary to the operation or maintenance of the establishment such as EQUIPMENT that is nonfunctional, no longer used and free of litter.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Unnecessary item(s)","subItem":"items that don't pertain to business","problemDescription":"Not removed from facility","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA / COOK LINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove from facility/premises."},{"inspectionid":"43933","inspectionDate":"10/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622507","name":"Xus China House Inc","violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"Hand sink(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."},{"inspectionid":"43933","inspectionDate":"10/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622507","name":"Xus China House Inc","violationCode":"3-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Cooling shall be accomplished in accordance with the time and temperature criteria specified under § 3-501.14 by using one or more of the following methods based on the type of FOOD being cooled:  \r\n   (1) Placing the FOOD in shallow pans; (Pf)\r\n   (2) Separating the FOOD into smaller or thinner portions; (Pf)\r\n   (3) Using rapid cooling EQUIPMENT; (Pf)\r\n   (4) Stirring the FOOD in a container placed in an ice water bath; (Pf)\r\n   (5) Using containers that facilitate heat transfer; (Pf)\r\n   (6) Adding ice as an ingredient; (Pf) or\r\n   (7) Other effective methods. (Pf)  \r\n(B) When placed in cooling or cold holding EQUIPMENT, FOOD containers in which FOOD is being cooled shall be:  \r\n   (1) Arranged in the EQUIPMENT to provide maximum heat transfer through the       container walls; and\r\n   (2) Loosely covered, or uncovered if protected from overhead contamination as          specified under Subparagraph 3-305.11(A)(2), during the cooling period to facilitate    heat transfer from the surface of the FOOD.","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food item(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly","subProblem":"Covered","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Cool items uncovered on the top shelf of cooler."},{"inspectionid":"43933","inspectionDate":"10/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622507","name":"Xus China House Inc","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"43933","inspectionDate":"10/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622507","name":"Xus China House Inc","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA / COOK LINE","subLocation":"Hand sink(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate sanitary hand drying aids/devices."},{"inspectionid":"43933","inspectionDate":"10/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622507","name":"Xus China House Inc","violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"To prevent contamination of food or food related items","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Food container(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store in manner that does not contaminate items"},{"inspectionid":"43933","inspectionDate":"10/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622507","name":"Xus China House Inc","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Less than","subProblem":"50 foot candles","location":"KITCHEN (BACK AREA)","subLocation":"Prep sink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"}]},{"inspectionid":"41925","establishmentid":"51622507","name":"Xus China House Inc","inspectionDate":"2018-03-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"1","pfcount":"2","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"3","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41925","inspectionDate":"3/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622507","name":"Xus China House Inc","violationCode":"6-501.114","violationDescription":"The PREMISES shall be free of items that are unnecessary to the operation or maintenance of the establishment such as EQUIPMENT that is nonfunctional, no longer used and free of litter.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Unnecessary item(s)","subItem":"items that don't pertain to business","problemDescription":"Not removed from facility","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN (BACK AREA)","subLocation":"Storage rack(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove from facility/premises."},{"inspectionid":"41925","inspectionDate":"3/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622507","name":"Xus China House Inc","violationCode":"3-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Cooling shall be accomplished in accordance with the time and temperature criteria specified under § 3-501.14 by using one or more of the following methods based on the type of FOOD being cooled:  \r\n   (1) Placing the FOOD in shallow pans; (Pf)\r\n   (2) Separating the FOOD into smaller or thinner portions; (Pf)\r\n   (3) Using rapid cooling EQUIPMENT; (Pf)\r\n   (4) Stirring the FOOD in a container placed in an ice water bath; (Pf)\r\n   (5) Using containers that facilitate heat transfer; (Pf)\r\n   (6) Adding ice as an ingredient; (Pf) or\r\n   (7) Other effective methods. (Pf)  \r\n(B) When placed in cooling or cold holding EQUIPMENT, FOOD containers in which FOOD is being cooled shall be:  \r\n   (1) Arranged in the EQUIPMENT to provide maximum heat transfer through the       container walls; and\r\n   (2) Loosely covered, or uncovered if protected from overhead contamination as          specified under Subparagraph 3-305.11(A)(2), during the cooling period to facilitate    heat transfer from the surface of the FOOD.","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food item(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly","subProblem":"Covered","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Cool items uncovered on the top shelf of cooler."},{"inspectionid":"41925","inspectionDate":"3/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622507","name":"Xus China House Inc","violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not accessible","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN (BACK AREA)","subLocation":"Hand sink(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Handwashing sinks are to be accessible for use at all times"},{"inspectionid":"41925","inspectionDate":"3/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622507","name":"Xus China House Inc","violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"Cooler (prep)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."}]},{"inspectionid":"39977","establishmentid":"51622507","name":"Xus China House Inc","inspectionDate":"2017-09-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"2","pfcount":"2","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"4","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"4","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"39977","inspectionDate":"9/5/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622507","name":"Xus China House Inc","violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"KITCHEN (BACK AREA)","subLocation":"Hand sink(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."},{"inspectionid":"39977","inspectionDate":"9/5/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622507","name":"Xus China House Inc","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Non-food contact surface(s)","subItem":"outsides of equipment","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN (BACK AREA)","subLocation":"Food storage bins-large","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"39977","inspectionDate":"9/5/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622507","name":"Xus China House Inc","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"CUSTOMER ORDER AREA","subLocation":"Cooler (beverage)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"inspectionid":"39977","inspectionDate":"9/5/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622507","name":"Xus China House Inc","violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All of the following food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American national standards institute, utilizing the conference for food protection standards:  (a) A food service establishment that is not any of the following:    (i) Operating under a temporary food service establishment license.  (ii) A vending machine location.     (b) An extended retail food establishment.  (c) Operated within a retail grocery.  (2) An individual certified under subsection (1) shall be recognized with full faith and credit by the state and all local units of government throughout the state.  (3) The department may promulgate rules to do all of the following:  (a) Develop requirements for retail food establishments to follow when employing certified food safety managers or personnel.  (b) Set a reasonable date for compliance with the requirements under subdivision (a) taking into consideration existing local personnel certification requirements.  (c) Establish certification fees necessary to implement, maintain, and track certified individuals directly or by contract. The department may annually adjust the schedule of fees to provide that the fee charged is sufficient to cover the cost of the certification tracking program.  (d) Implement and enforce the requirements described in subdivision (a).    (4) The certification program developed by the American national standards institute, as it exists on April 1, 2008 , is incorporated by reference. The department may adopt updates to the certification program accreditation standards in subsection (1) by rule.     (5) This section does not prohibit any local legislative body from implementing a food handler program, an employee health certification program, or a manager certification program, if it is not in conflict with this section.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"39977","inspectionDate":"9/5/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622507","name":"Xus China House Inc","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"NON FOOD CONTACT SURFACES","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"inspectionid":"39977","inspectionDate":"9/5/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622507","name":"Xus China House Inc","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622507"}}